<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Showcase on LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/tags/showcase/</link><description>Recent content in Showcase on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:48:49 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.localstack.cloud/tags/showcase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mastering AWS Infrastructure Testing with LocalStack Cloud Pods - on localhost, CI and Testcontainers</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-20-cloud-pods-local-to-ci-and-testcontainers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-20-cloud-pods-local-to-ci-and-testcontainers/</guid><description>Cloud Pods, State &amp;amp; Persistence in the LocalStack ecosystem In a few words, LocalStack is a cloud service emulator that allows you to develop and test your cloud and serverless applications locally by replicating AWS environments on any machine without the need to deploy them to the actual AWS cloud. This tool provides an easy and cost-effective way to test cloud applications by locally providing all the necessary dependencies.
LocalStack ships as a Docker container, making its state ephemeral by default.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack Neptune development with G.V() — Gremlin IDE</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-05-localstack-neptune-development-with-gv-gremlin-ide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-05-localstack-neptune-development-with-gv-gremlin-ide/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack offers a rich cloud development framework to emulate the functionality of many AWS services locally at a fraction of the cost and effort. It supports developers with facilities to build, test and launch complex applications locally, including services such as the Amazon Neptune.
However, interacting with Amazon Neptune can be challenging due to the lack of easy-to-use tools, as well as the learning curve associated with graph databases and their querying languages.</description></item><item><title>Building LocalStack with LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-08-building-localstack-with-localstack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-08-building-localstack-with-localstack/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Pro was announced in 2019, shipping along with it the LocalStack Web application to support developer toolings &amp;amp; features to make local cloud development a breeze. As our team expanded and we envisioned a broader scope for the LocalStack product, we started dogfooding our software to leverage the same features our customers use LocalStack for.
LocalStack’s core cloud emulator allows us to run our own cloud application - including its infrastructure - locally, which provides an efficient developer experience at the start of the entire software development lifecycle (SDLC).</description></item><item><title>Ephemeral Environments with LocalStack &amp; Shipyard</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-22-ephemeral-environments-with-localstack-shipyard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-22-ephemeral-environments-with-localstack-shipyard/</guid><description>Introduction We’re excited to announce our partnership with Shipyard, the ephemeral environment self-service platform, that allows you to spin up on-demand preview deployments via Kubernetes clusters to turbocharge your application lifecycle. With Shipyard, you can now deploy your cloud applications in short-lived environments to enable developer teams to run tests, preview features, and get alignment with cross-departmental projects. Shipyard also enables application previews on every pull request and simplifies monitoring, debugging, and deployment all from one dashboard!</description></item><item><title>Exploring S3 Mocking Tools — A Comparative Analysis of S3Mock, MinIO, and LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-08-exploring-s3-mocking-tools-a-comparative-analysis-of-s3mock-minio-and-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-08-exploring-s3-mocking-tools-a-comparative-analysis-of-s3mock-minio-and-localstack/</guid><description>Introduction Amazon S3 (Simple Storage Service) is a scalable and durable cloud object storage service offered by AWS. It plays a crucial role in cloud computing by allowing developers to store and retrieve data anywhere on the web. For development and testing purposes, local alternatives to S3 are convenient to avoid the time and cost of developing and debugging applications directly on the cloud. This blog post delves into a comprehensive comparison of popular tools that emulate S3 locally, exploring their strengths, weaknesses, and performance aspects.</description></item><item><title>Add Authentication &amp; Authorization to LocalStack with the Authress extension</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-07-add-authentication-authorization-to-localstack-with-the-authress-extension/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-07-add-authentication-authorization-to-localstack-with-the-authress-extension/</guid><description>Introduction The Authress extension for LocalStack, our first community extension, enables running Authress directly on your machine. It provides a high-fidelity, fully local authentication and authorization service, which bypasses the need to rely on the live version for local development.
Ensuring your users can access your software while maintaining the privacy of their data and clean tenant separation is not a trivial challenge. It’s not just about supporting different login mechanisms and protecting the personal data included in the user identity.</description></item><item><title>AWS re:Invent - Ten Things You Need to Know About LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-27-ten-things-you-need-to-know-about-localstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-27-ten-things-you-need-to-know-about-localstack/</guid><description>In an era dominated by cloud computing, developing and testing software locally before deploying it to the cloud for production is essential, as it allows for thorough, controlled testing environments, quicker iteration, and reduced dependency on cloud resources during the development phase, leading to more robust and reliable cloud-deployed applications.
Here at AWS re:Invent, a recurring question captures our attention: &amp;ldquo;What is LocalStack?&amp;quot; - A query that sparks conversations about innovation, local development solutions, and the seamless transition to the cloud environment.</description></item><item><title>Develop your Cloudflare Workers + AWS apps locally with LocalStack &amp; Miniflare</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</guid><description>LocalStack is a cloud development platform that turbocharges your cloud application development &amp;amp; testing, fosters team collaboration, and provides an integrated cloud developer experience with a local cloud sandbox. LocalStack’s core cloud emulator runs inside a Docker container and provides a set of external network ports for integrations, SDKs, or CI providers for developers to execute their cloud &amp;amp; serverless applications fully locally without talking to the real cloud services. This enables a highly efficient development loop, by reducing the feedback cycles from minutes to seconds.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack x Gitpod - Run cloud applications with LocalStack and Gitpod</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2022-09-26-localstack-x-gitpod-run-cloud-applications-with-localstack-and-gitpod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 11:31:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2022-09-26-localstack-x-gitpod-run-cloud-applications-with-localstack-and-gitpod/</guid><description>Shipping applications to production requires them to be battle-tested in the dev environment. The dev environment should mimic the production environment as closely as possible. This comes with a cost: testing cloud applications is cumbersome as they have many moving parts. For instance, if you build a simple Lambda function in AWS, you might use services such as CloudWatch, S3, IAM, etc.
Imagine configuring your project and provisioning these cloud resources in a test environment every time for developing new features.</description></item><item><title>Test Monitoring for LocalStack Apps</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2021-09-16-test-monitoring-for-localstack-apps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 13:10:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2021-09-16-test-monitoring-for-localstack-apps/</guid><description>📢 Thundra Inc and its product Foresight have ceased operations and have been acquired by Catchpoint, resulting in significant changes to their products and services. Please note that the tutorial provided in our blog may no longer be applicable or functional with the latest updates. We are keeping this blog post available for informational purposes only. LocalStack gives developers the freedom to develop their cloud applications locally (even offline) - enabling a highly efficient dev&amp;amp;test loop.</description></item></channel></rss>