<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harsh Mishra on LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/contributors/harsh-mishra/</link><description>Recent content in Harsh Mishra on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.localstack.cloud/contributors/harsh-mishra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simulating outages for local cloud apps with LocalStack Chaos API</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-08-26-simulating-outages-for-local-cloud-apps-with-localstack-chaos-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-08-26-simulating-outages-for-local-cloud-apps-with-localstack-chaos-api/</guid><description>Introduction Regardless of the precautions you take in developing your application and the reliability of cloud providers like AWS, incidents are unavoidable. They can be anything from as large-scale regional outage to as small as a request failing for reasons perhaps unknown. Common examples might include:
Region-wide outages DNS failovers Service failures Network faults The key is in building your application in such a way that it handles these situations gracefully.</description></item><item><title>Celebrating 50,000 GitHub Stars for LocalStack!</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-01-03-celebrating-50k-github-stars-localstack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-01-03-celebrating-50k-github-stars-localstack/</guid><description>Seven years ago, on August 16, 2016, the LocalStack project was born. The journey since then has been nothing short of incredible. LocalStack has now crossed 50,000 stars on GitHub after three major releases and dozens of minor releases. For the past 16 months since LocalStack 1.0 went live, it has been on a consistent upward trajectory, and we are proud of everyone who is discovering, starring, and joining our project &amp;amp; community!</description></item><item><title>LocalStack Neptune development with G.V() — Gremlin IDE</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-05-localstack-neptune-development-with-gv-gremlin-ide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-05-localstack-neptune-development-with-gv-gremlin-ide/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack offers a rich cloud development framework to emulate the functionality of many AWS services locally at a fraction of the cost and effort. It supports developers with facilities to build, test and launch complex applications locally, including services such as the Amazon Neptune.
However, interacting with Amazon Neptune can be challenging due to the lack of easy-to-use tools, as well as the learning curve associated with graph databases and their querying languages.</description></item><item><title>Building LocalStack with LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-08-building-localstack-with-localstack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-08-building-localstack-with-localstack/</guid><description>Introduction LocalStack Pro was announced in 2019, shipping along with it the LocalStack Web application to support developer toolings &amp;amp; features to make local cloud development a breeze. As our team expanded and we envisioned a broader scope for the LocalStack product, we started dogfooding our software to leverage the same features our customers use LocalStack for.
LocalStack’s core cloud emulator allows us to run our own cloud application - including its infrastructure - locally, which provides an efficient developer experience at the start of the entire software development lifecycle (SDLC).</description></item><item><title>Ephemeral Environments with LocalStack &amp; Shipyard</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-22-ephemeral-environments-with-localstack-shipyard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-04-22-ephemeral-environments-with-localstack-shipyard/</guid><description>Introduction We’re excited to announce our partnership with Shipyard, the ephemeral environment self-service platform, that allows you to spin up on-demand preview deployments via Kubernetes clusters to turbocharge your application lifecycle. With Shipyard, you can now deploy your cloud applications in short-lived environments to enable developer teams to run tests, preview features, and get alignment with cross-departmental projects. Shipyard also enables application previews on every pull request and simplifies monitoring, debugging, and deployment all from one dashboard!</description></item><item><title>Add Authentication &amp; Authorization to LocalStack with the Authress extension</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-07-add-authentication-authorization-to-localstack-with-the-authress-extension/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-02-07-add-authentication-authorization-to-localstack-with-the-authress-extension/</guid><description>Introduction The Authress extension for LocalStack, our first community extension, enables running Authress directly on your machine. It provides a high-fidelity, fully local authentication and authorization service, which bypasses the need to rely on the live version for local development.
Ensuring your users can access your software while maintaining the privacy of their data and clean tenant separation is not a trivial challenge. It’s not just about supporting different login mechanisms and protecting the personal data included in the user identity.</description></item><item><title>One Click Local Development: Announcing Leapp's LocalStack Integration</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-12-18-one-click-local-development-announcing-leapps-localstack-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-12-18-one-click-local-development-announcing-leapps-localstack-integration/</guid><description>LocalStack enables a fully functional cloud stack to emulate AWS cloud services on your local machine. It allows developers to shorten their feedback loop by enabling them to develop, test, and deploy their applications locally while reducing costs and improving agility.
LocalStack supports integration wrappers for AWS CLI, CDK, Terraform, to enable developers to connect to the local cloud emulator. However, maintaining these wrappers requires additional effort, and developers would like to switch from AWS to LocalStack in a click.</description></item><item><title>Develop your Cloudflare Workers + AWS apps locally with LocalStack &amp; Miniflare</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-06-26-develop-your-cloudflare-workers-aws-apps-locally-with-localstack-miniflare/</guid><description>LocalStack is a cloud development platform that turbocharges your cloud application development &amp;amp; testing, fosters team collaboration, and provides an integrated cloud developer experience with a local cloud sandbox. LocalStack’s core cloud emulator runs inside a Docker container and provides a set of external network ports for integrations, SDKs, or CI providers for developers to execute their cloud &amp;amp; serverless applications fully locally without talking to the real cloud services. This enables a highly efficient development loop, by reducing the feedback cycles from minutes to seconds.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Docker Extension for Docker Desktop</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-01-13-introducing-localstack-extension-for-docker-desktop/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-01-13-introducing-localstack-extension-for-docker-desktop/</guid><description>We are excited to announce the release of the LocalStack Docker Extension to help developers run their cloud &amp;amp; serverless applications locally. With our Docker Extension, developers can capitalize on a fully-integrated experience to manage their LocalStack image, configuration profiles, and container logs directly within the Docker Desktop. Docker Extensions was officially announced last year to help communities integrate new functionalities with the Docker Desktop, and we have worked closely with the Docker team to develop our extension!</description></item><item><title>Contribute to Open Source With LocalStack &amp; Hacktoberfest</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2022-10-01-contribute-to-open-source-with-localstack-hacktoberfest/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s October 2022, and we have a few surprises already in store for our open-source community. LocalStack is participating in Hacktoberfest 2022, a month-long open-source program to promote and bolster open-source contribution and collaboration! We are opening up projects to contribute to for our first Hacktoberfest, and we are incredibly excited to welcome new first-time contributors to our community and celebrate their contributions!
If you have always been interested &amp;amp; intrigued by open-source and LocalStack but don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start, then Hacktoberfest is a perfect place for you to start.</description></item></channel></rss>