<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LocalStack Team on LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/</link><description>Recent content in LocalStack Team on LocalStack</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.localstack.cloud/contributors/localstack-team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LocalStack Named to Redpoint InfraRed 100 List</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-18-redpoint-infrared-100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-06-18-redpoint-infrared-100/</guid><description>New York, NY – June 18, 2024 – LocalStack, the leading tool for cloud infrastructure emulation, is thrilled to announce its inclusion in the 2024 Redpoint InfraRed 100 list. This prestigious recognition not only honors the top 100 private companies poised to lead the next wave of innovation in the cloud infrastructure market but also underscores LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s significant impact on the industry. Redpoint Ventures, renowned for backing transformative companies such as Snowflake, Netflix, Stripe, Twilio, and HashiCorp, launched the InfraRed 100 to spotlight emerging industry leaders.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack for Snowflake: The new emulator to build &amp; test data pipelines locally</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-22-introducing-localstack-for-snowflake/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-05-22-introducing-localstack-for-snowflake/</guid><description>Introduction We are excited to announce the public preview of LocalStack for Snowflake ❄️. This new emulator enables you to develop and test your Snowflake data applications locally and in CI pipelines, using a Docker container that can be easily plugged into your Snowflake integrations, such as Snowpark, different client libraries, or Streamlit applications, among others. This preview version of the Snowflake emulator supports various key features, such as:
DDL/DML/DQL operations on warehouses, databases, schemas, and tables; Storing files in Snowflake stages; Tasks for scheduled execution; Snowpipe streaming with Kafka connector; User-defined functions (UDFs) in JavaScript and Python; Table streams for change data capture (CDC) and audit logs; Cross-database resource sharing; Basic support for running Streamlit applications locally; Infrastructure-as-code with Terraform &amp;amp; Pulumi; Test your data applications in Continuous Integration (CI) pipelines with GitHub Actions, CircleCI &amp;amp; GitLab CI (among others); Enterprise-tested features like Cloud Pods and Persistence for state snapshots.</description></item><item><title>CartonCloud utilizes LocalStack for transforming development efficiency and agility!</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-03-28-localstack-cartoncloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-03-28-localstack-cartoncloud/</guid><description>“LocalStack has massively decreased the time when the local environment is breaking for our developers. That was a big pain point, and it&amp;rsquo;s not anymore!”
Vincent Fletcher,
Co-Founder &amp; Chief Product Office at CartonCloud
CartonCloud is a cloud-based Transport Management System (TMS) and Warehouse Management System (WMS) designed specifically for the SME market, streamlining end-to-end business logistics operations. With a client base extending across Australia, New Zealand, and North America, CartonCloud's central operating system plays a crucial role in facilitating communication between administration staff, drivers, and warehouse personnel on a day-to-day basis.</description></item><item><title>Neurolytics enhances the efficiency and agility of its cloud-based development with LocalStack</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-01-25-localstack-neurolyticsai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2024-01-25-localstack-neurolyticsai/</guid><description>“LocalStack has made cloud development easier to test and debug, significantly reducing our development and testing loops by approximately 30%. This enables faster iterations and quicker feature releases and translates to substantial financial savings.”
Yashar Hosseinpour,
Lead Developer at Neurolytics
Neurolytics, a startup in the field of behavioral analysis, has developed a platform for enhancing the recruitment process through AI-driven video analysis. Their solution offers a transformative approach for companies and job candidates, ensuring a match between their profiles and the company culture.</description></item><item><title>Announcing LocalStack 3.0 General Availability!</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-16-announcing-localstack-30-general-availability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-16-announcing-localstack-30-general-availability/</guid><description>Today, we are excited to announce LocalStack 3.0, our latest major release aiming to empower developers with a high-fidelity local cloud development &amp;amp; testing experience. Earlier this year, we unveiled LocalStack 2.0, which brought forth many new features and improvements, along with better integration with the AWS tooling ecosystem. With the 3.0 release, we’re doubling down on our promise to boost developer productivity and tackle the issues that often slow down cloud software development and delivery workflows — specifically, simplifying onboarding and eliminating the inefficiencies that lead to prolonged development and test cycles.</description></item><item><title>Introducing LocalStack Desktop Application for local cloud development &amp; testing</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-09-introducing-localstack-desktop-application-for-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that we have released an all-new Desktop Application to make cloud development with LocalStack a breeze! The Desktop application underscores our unwavering commitment to make LocalStack accessible for our users, who would like to use a local cloud sandbox for development, testing, and experimentation, and truly embrace the inner dev loop. LocalStack enables users to control, manage, and visualize over 80+ emulated AWS cloud services, running entirely on your local machine.</description></item><item><title>Join LocalStack at AWS re:Invent 2023</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-11-09-join-localstack-at-aws-reinvent-2023/</guid><description>LocalStack is excited to be participating in AWS re:Invent 2023, Amazon&amp;rsquo;s premier annual cloud computing conference. Amidst keynote addresses, an array of technical sessions, and a bustling expo floor designed for learning and networking, we&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce our role as an Exhibit Sponsor for this year&amp;rsquo;s event.
Join us at Booth #1074 (Map) in the Venetian Expo, Las Vegas, from November 27 to December 1. It&amp;rsquo;s an opportune moment to engage with the LocalStack team, where we&amp;rsquo;ll not only share our insights but also learn valuable lessons from your experiences.</description></item><item><title>OpenFABR leverages LocalStack for local Infrastructure as Code development and validation</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-09-25-case-study-openfabr/</guid><description>“LocalStack has revolutionized our development process by providing seamless Infrastructure-as-Code validation, rapid resource spin-up, and streamlined testing. It&amp;rsquo;s an essential component of our development toolkit and has greatly enhanced our team&amp;rsquo;s agility &amp;amp; efficiency.”
Janaka Abeywardhana,
Co-Founder — CPTO at FABR
FABR is a cloud infrastructure and tooling company that addresses critical challenges in building and managing cloud infrastructure for application development across multiple public cloud providers.</description></item><item><title>LocalStack has joined AWS Marketplace to streamline local cloud development &amp; testing!</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-09-07-localstack-has-joined-aws-marketplace-to-streamline-local-cloud-development-testing/</guid><description>We are excited to announce that LocalStack is now available in the AWS Marketplace. LocalStack is the leading platform for local development and testing of cloud applications. LocalStack&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Emulator allows you to effectively run over 80 AWS services directly on your local machine and on CI/CD systems to significantly cut down on development time and feedback cycles. At its core, LocalStack provides a growing ecosystem of native integrations that encompasses crucial components such as CI/CD providers, application development frameworks, programming language SDKs, Infrastructure-as-Code tools, and more.</description></item><item><title>Xiatech accelerates their development workflows on cloud using LocalStack!</title><link>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.localstack.cloud/2023-07-05-case-study-xiatech/</guid><description>“Our engineering team utilizes LocalStack to provide a complete, localized AWS environment where developers can build, test, profile and debug infrastructure and code ahead of deployment to the cloud.”
Rick Timmis,
Head of Engineering at Xiatech
Xiatech helps organizations and users connect systems, unify data, and make data-driven decisions with artificial intelligence via a continuous flow of actionable insights. Xiatech’s flagship platform is Xfuze, a hyper-integration platform that helps customers gain key insights, create value from data and turbocharge legacy technology investments.</description></item></channel></rss>